https://norcalbma.org/privacy-policy/

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Privacy Policy
Spread the loveNORCALBMA.ORG as the owner and manager of the website you visit, sets out in this section the Privacy Policy in use, and on the personal information that the user can provide when visiting or browsing the website owned by us.
In the treatment of personal data, NORCALBMA.ORG guarantees compliance with Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13, on the Protection of Personal Data and its implementing regulations, Royal Decree 1720/2007, of 21 December, by which its Regulations are approved, as well as the LSSICE 34/2002, of July 11, of the Information Society and Electronic Commerce.
NORCALBMA.ORG reserves the right to modify this Data Protection Policy at any time, in order to adapt it to new legislation or changes in its activities, the one published at any time on our website being in force.
QUALITY AND PURPOSE
By clicking on the “Send” button (or equivalent) incorporated in our forms, the user declares that the information and data provided therein are accurate and truthful. So that the information provided is always updated and does not contain errors, the User must communicate, as soon as possible, the modifications of their personal data that are produced, as well as the rectifications of erroneous data in case it detects any. The User guarantees that the data provided is true, exact, complete and up-to-date, being responsible for any direct or indirect damage or harm that may be caused as a consequence of the breach of such obligation. Depending on the form and / or email you access, or send, the information you provide will be used for the purposes described below, for which you expressly and freely and unequivocally accept its treatment according to the following purposes:
Those that are particularly indicated on each of the pages where the electronic registration form appears.
In general, to meet your requests, queries, comments, orders or any type of request that is made by the user through any of the contact forms that we make available to our users, followers or readers.
To inform you about queries, requests, activities, products, news and / or services; via e-mail, fax, WhatsApp, Skype, phone provided, social communities (Social Networks), and likewise to send you commercial communications through any other electronic or physical means. These communications will always be related to our theme, services, news or promotions, as well as those that you consider of interest and that may be offered by collaborators, companies or partners with whom we have commercial promotion agreements. If so, we guarantee that these third parties will never have access to your personal data. Being in any case these communications made by NORCALBMA.ORG, and always on products and services related to our sector.
Prepare market profiles for advertising or statistical purposes.
The same information may be offered or sent to you by becoming a follower of the NORCALBMA.ORG profiles  on the social networks that link this Website, so by becoming a follower of either of the two you expressly consent to the processing of your personal data within the environment of these social networks, in compliance with these, as well as their particular conditions and privacy policies. If you wish to stop receiving such information or have this data cancelled, you can unsubscribe as a follower of our profiles on these networks. In addition, followers on social networks may exercise the rights that the Law confers on them, although, since these platforms belong to third parties, the responses to the exercise of rights by the NORCALBMA.ORG will be limited by the functionalities allowed by the social network in question, so we recommend that before following our profiles on social networks, you review the conditions of use and their privacy policies.
UNSUBSCRIBE TO NEWSLETTER AND SENDING COMMERCIAL COMMUNICATIONS
In compliance with the LSSI-CE 34/2002, of July 11, of the Information Society and Electronic Commerce, we inform you that you may at any time  revoke the consent given  for the sending of commercial communications, or to cause cancellation of our subscription services, just by sending an email indicating your request to:  Contact US indicating: UNDER SUBSCRIPTION MARKETINGCULTURAL.ONLINE
THIRD PARTY DATA
In the event that you provide us with personal data of third parties, in compliance with the provisions of article 5.4. LOPD, you  declare to have informed said persons  previously , of the content of the data provided, of the origin thereof, of the existence and purpose of the file where their data is contained, of the recipients of said information, of the possibility of exercise the rights of access, rectification, cancellation or opposition, as well as the identifying data of NORCALBMA.ORG In this sense, it is your sole responsibility to inform third parties whose data you are going to give us, not assuming NORCALBMA.ORG no responsibility for the breach of this provision by the user.
EXERCISE OF RIGHTS
The owner of the data may exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition by contacting NORCALBMA.ORG through   Said request must contain the following information: name and surname, address for notification purposes, photocopy of DNI I or Passport.
SECURITY MEASURES
NORCALBMA.ORG has adopted all the technical and organizational measures necessary to guarantee the security and integrity of the personal data it deals with, as well as to prevent its loss, alteration and / or access by unauthorized third parties. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the user acknowledges and accepts that Internet security measures are not impregnable
Popular articles
6 Anti-Aging Home Remedies That Make Wonders on Skin!
Health November 21, 2020
Loot boxes: I blew my parents’ savings gaming on Fifa
News July 9, 2020
Birmingham-based Help Lightning raises $8 million for its remote training and...
News August 16, 2020
Apple has €13bn Irish tax bill overturned
News July 15, 2020
Rental e-scooters to be made legal on UK roads from Saturday
News June 30, 2020
Categories
Education
Entertainment
Health
News
Review
Tech
Follow Us
Get new posts by email
ABOUT USNorcalbma.org, the pioneer of news sources in India operates under the philosophy of keeping its readers informed. Norcalbma.org tells the story of India and it offers fresh, compelling content that’s useful and informative for its readers. Norcalbma.org delivers the latest updates on national and international issues with photo, audio and video. Norcalbma.org strives to be very accurate by leaving no stone unturned as it digs into the heart of every story on the local as well as international level.
CONTACT US
ABOUT US
Privacy Policy
DMCA
DISCLAIMER
Copyright © 2020 Norcalbma.org All Rights Reserved.
